AD-FREE LOGIN

* Ad-Free Login

Tough Times
===========

Demand honest news. Help support AlterNet and our mission to keep you informed during this crisis.

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Policy**

AlterNet and our parent organization, AlterNet Media, respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our website, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. When you use our website, we share information that we collect from you, such as your email (in hashed form), IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with our partner/service provider, LiveRamp Inc. LiveRamp returns an online identification code that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online and cross-channel advertising and it may be shared with advertising companies to enable interest-based and targeted advertising. To opt out of this use, please click here (https://optout.liveramp.com/opt\_out)

**Traffic Data**

When you visit AlterNet, our systems collect basic information about your computer, including: IP address (your computer's unique signature), operating system, browser software (e.g. Chrome, Firefox, Safari), and internet service provider (e.g., Comcast, AT&T, etc.). We also collect information about what you view on the site to help us optimize content.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Use of Cookies**

AlterNet employs cookies—small text files placed on your computer's hard drive—to track the type of content and sites to which our users link, the length of time they spend at any particular site and the AlterNet services they use. Cookies also help us diagnose problems with our server.

For more on cookies, please [click here](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).

**Email Newsletters and "Send a Friend" Feature**

After signing up online, users will receive email newsletters and other occasional announcements from AlterNet. In order to distribute our email, we collect subscribers' email addresses. We do not share addresses with other companies or partners. Users can unsubscribe from email newsletters at any time.

AlterNet offers a "send this story to a friend" feature, which allows our users to inform others about an article they might be interested in. For this feature to function, we ask for email addresses from the sender and for the recipient. We do not store or save these addresses and you will not receive any communication from AlterNet or its partners as a result of having used this feature.

**Discussion Forums**

AlterNet makes comment [feedback forums](https://disqus.com/home/forum/alternet/) available to its users. Please remember any information disclosed in these areas becomes publicly available, and therefore you should exercise caution when disclosing personal information.

If you have any concerns about this, send email to [discuss@alternet.org](mailto:discuss@alternet.org).

**Surveys**

From time to time AlterNet will conduct voluntary surveys of site visitors to obtain aggregate demographic information about them. This information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals.

**Linking to Other Sites**

AlterNet contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Children's Guidelines**

Protecting the rights of children is important to us. As a result, we do not collect or maintain any information from individuals we know to be under 13 years old, and no part of AlterNet is intended to attract anyone under 13.

**Unsubscribe, Data Removal and Data Modification Policies**

AlterNet allows users to opt out of receiving communications from us and to modify or remove their information from our system. The following options are available to do so:

* Send email to [support@alternet.org](mailto:support@alternet.org)
* Send mail to: AlterNet, PO Box 21040, Washington, D.C. 20009

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

AlterNet will not use or disclose your personal information, except (i) as described in this privacy policy, (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or (iii) to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, or other sale or transfer of some or all of AlterNet Media's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by AlterNet Media about our website users is among the assets transferred. In case of disclosure of personal information in the event of a sale or transfer of some or all of AlterNet Media's assets, you may direct us not to transfer your personal information at any time by contacting us at the address below or by sending an email to [info@alternet.org](mailto:info@alternet.org). This policy does not protect information you post to any online bulletin board or other public forum within our website.

**Contacting AlterNet**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this website, you can contact: AlterNet Media, PO Box 21040, Washington, DC 20009 and [info@alternet.org](mailto:info@alternet.org). AlterNet Media reserves the right to amend this Privacy Statement at any time without notice, and only the current Privacy Statement may be deemed effective.

@2024 - AlterNet Media Inc. All Rights Reserved. - "Poynter" fonts provided by fontsempire.com.
